The Labor Historians Bulletin /3079
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
The Labor Historians Bulletin
1953-1959
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations, University of Illinois
/3079
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
History-related disciplines, periodicals.
Collection of Bulletin volumes between 1953 and 1959.
1288061
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 12, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4012: Kheel Center Files and Circulation Reserve List
Working class -- History -- Periodicals; Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations, Univesity of Illinois
1288061
- Labor Historians Bulletin v.1:no.1 July 1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Labor Historians Bulletin September/December, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Labor Historians Bulletin April, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Labor Historians Bulletin July, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Labor Historians Bulletin Fall, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Labor Historians Bulletin Winter, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Labor Historians Bulletin Spring, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Labor Historians Bulletin Summer, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Labor Historians Bulletin v.4:no.1 Fall 1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Labor Historians Bulletin v.4:no.2 Winter 1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Labor Historians Bulletin v.4:no.3 Spring 1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Labor Historians Bulletin v.4:no.3 Summer 1957 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Labor Historians Bulletin v.4:no.4 Fall 1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Labor Historians Bulletin v.5:no.2 Winter 1958 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Labor Historians Bulletin v.5:no.3 Spring 1958 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Labor Historians Bulletin v.5 and 6:no.1 and 4 Summer and Fall 1958 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Labor Historians Bulletin 5-6:no.2 Winter, 1958-59, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Labor Historians Bulletin v.6:no.3 Spring 1959 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Labor Historians Bulletin v.6:no.4 Summer and Fall '59, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 19)